no data All-Time Top Goal Scorers
Harry Souttar (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 36 | Goals: 11 | Assists: no data
Mark Viduka (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 43 | Goals: 11 | Assists: no data
Dave Harding (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 45 | Goals: 11 | Assists: no data
Jackson Irvine (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 76 | Goals: 11 | Assists: no data
Mitchell Duke (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 45 | Goals: 12 | Assists: no data
Scott Chipperfield (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 68 | Goals: 12 | Assists: no data
Jack Hughes (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 9 | Goals: 13 | Assists: no data
Paul Trimboli (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 40 | Goals: 13 | Assists: no data
Mark Bresciano (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 84 | Goals: 13 | Assists: no data
Frank Parsons (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 5 | Goals: 14 | Assists: no data
Judy Masters (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 10 | Goals: 14 | Assists: no data
Frank Farina (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 67 | Goals: 14 | Assists: no data
Mathew Leckie (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 79 | Goals: 14 | Assists: no data
Eddie Krncevic (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 35 | Goals: 17 | Assists: no data
Ray Baartz (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 46 | Goals: 17 | Assists: no data
Harry Kewell (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 58 | Goals: 17 | Assists: no data
Aurelio Vidmar (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 53 | Goals: 18 | Assists: no data
Graham Arnold (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 56 | Goals: 19 | Assists: no data
Joshua Kennedy (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 36 | Goals: 20 | Assists: no data
Gary Cole (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 40 | Goals: 20 | Assists: no data
Mile Jedinak (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 79 | Goals: 20 | Assists: no data
Brett Emerton (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 95 | Goals: 20 | Assists: no data
David Zdrilic (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 31 | Goals: 21 | Assists: no data
John Kosmina (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 60 | Goals: 25 | Assists: no data
Attila Abonyi (Australia) - no data
John Aloisi (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 55 | Goals: 27 | Assists: no data
Archie Thompson (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 54 | Goals: 28 | Assists: no data
George Smith (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 13 | Goals: 29 | Assists: no data
Damian Mori (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 45 | Goals: 29 | Assists: no data
Tim Cahill (Australia) - no data
Appearances: 108 | Goals: 50 | Assists: no data